Guide to the Mexican movie stills, 1937-1985
Department of Special Collections
Mexican movie stills,
1937-1985
M1049
10 linear ft. (7,124 photographs from 606 movies)
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
This collection contains still images from 606 movies from the heyday of the Mexican movie industry. The collection is a rich pictorial resource documenting hundreds of Mexican actors and actresses.
Administrative Information
Access
None.
Acquisition Information
Purchased, 1999.
Collection Scope and Content Summary
This collection contains still images from 606 movies from the heyday of the Mexican movie industry. The collection is a rich pictorial resource documenting hundreds of Mexican actors and actresses.
Access Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Motion pictures--Mexico--History.; Photographs.; Stills (Motion pictures); Photoprints.
Collection Contents
- A La Sombra Del Sol 1965, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- A Los Cuatro Vientos 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- A Ritmo De Twist 1962, 7 Stills (Box 1)
- A.T.M. 1951, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Abandonadas, Las 1944, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Abuelita A Tomica, Una 1958, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Acorralados 1975, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Adorable Sinverguenza, Un 1983, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Adorables Mujercitas, Las 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Adorada Enemiga 1963, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Adriana Del Rio Actriz 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Adultera, La 1956, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- A Gente Via Jero, El 1974, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Aguila Osol 1937, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Ahi Es Ta El Detalle 1940, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Ahi Viene Martin Corona 1951, 9 Stills (Box 1)
- Ahorcado, El 1983, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Al Diablo Las Mujeres 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Al Fin Solos 1968, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Albures Mexicanos 1983, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Alguiennos Quiere Ma Tar 1969, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Alma De Br Once 1944, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Alma Grande 1965, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Alma Grande En El Desierto 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Alla Enla Plaza Garibaldi 1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Amante Anda Suelto, Un 1969, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Amantes Del Desierto, Los 1957, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Amar Fuesupecado 1950, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Amargura Demiraza, La 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Amor Enlasnubes 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 1)
- Amor Extrano, Un 1974, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Amor Libre 1978, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Amor Se Dice Cantando 1957, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Angel V Yo, El 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Angelitos Negros 1948, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Anima De Sa Yula, El 1974, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Apando, El 1975, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Apariencias Enga Na N, Las 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Aqui Estanlosaguilares 1956, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Ardiente Deseo, El 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Arte De Enganar, El 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Asesinos En La Noche 1956, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Audaz Y Bravero 1964, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Aventurasdejoselito Ypulgarcito, Las 1959, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Aventura S De Pito Perez, Las 1956, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Aventuras De Un Caballo Blanco V Unnino 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Aventuras De Un Mexicano Enafrica 1948, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Aychabela 1960, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Banda Del Fantasma Negro, La 1963, 10 Stills (Box 2)
- Barchante Neguib, El 1945, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Barridos Yregados 1961, 8 Stills (Box 2)
- Barrio Bajo 1950, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Barrio De Campeones 1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Bella Otero, La 1954, 8 Stills (Box 2)
- Besos Prohibidos 1956, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Bestias Juveniles 111970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Bienamada, La 1951, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Bikinis V Rock 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Blanco, Lo Rojo Ylo Negro, Lo 1978, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 2)
- Bombero A Tomico, El 1950, 8 Stills (Box 2)
- Boxeador, El 1957) Buscona, La, 1969 (Box 3)
- Cabal Ga Nd 0 A La L Una 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Cada Quiensumusica 1958, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Cadena Dementiras 1955, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Café Colon 1958, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Cain, Abel Yel Otro 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Cain Del Bajio, El 1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Cala Vera Negra, La 1959, 9 Stills (Box 3)
- Camino, Un 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Camino De Guanajuato 1955)' (Box 3)
- Campeon Ciclista, El 1956, 10 Stills (Box 3)
- Campeones Del Ring 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Campeones Justicieros, Los 1970, 10 Stills (Box 3)
- Cancionde Cuna 1952, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Cancion Del Alma 1963, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Cancionpara Recordar, Una 1958, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Cantando Na Ce El Amor 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Ca P1 Tande Rurales, Un 1950, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Captura De Gabino Barrera, La 1967, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Capulina Contra Los Monstruos 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Caras Nuevas 1955, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Carcachita, La 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Carcel De Laredo, La 1983, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Carinosas, Las 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Carita, El 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Carita De Cielo 1946, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Carnemanda,La 1947, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Casa De Las Mucha Chas, La 1968, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Casa Del Terror, La 1959, 7 Stills (Box 3)
- Cascabel 1976, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 3)
- Caso De La Mujer Asesinadita, El 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Caso De Unadolescente, El 1957, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Casto Susano, El 1952, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Cazadores De Cabezas 1960, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Ceniciento, El 1951, 6 Stills (Box 4)
- Cenizas Del Diputado, Las 1976, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Claudia Y El Deseo 1968, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Click Fotografo De Model 05 1968, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Color De Nuestra Piel, El 1982, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Comandante Furia, El 1965, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Comezon Del Amor, La 1959, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Comicosdela Legua 1956, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Complotmongol, El 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Con Licencia Para Ma Tar 1967, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Con Quienandannuestras Hijas? 1955, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Con Quienandan Nuestros Locos 1960, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Concurso De Belleza 1957, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Contigoa La Distancia 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Contra Ba Nd 0 For Amor 1978, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Contrabando V Traicion 1975, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Corazon Sal Vaje 1955, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Corona De Un Campeon, La 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Correo Del Norte, El 1960, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Corrompidos, Los 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Cortesana 1947, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Crimen V Castigo 1950, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Cristo Teama 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Cronica De Unamor 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Cronica Roja 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 4)
- Cruz De Olvido1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Cuando Las Mujeres Mandan 1950, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Cuando Levanta La Niebla 1952, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Cuando Los Hijos Odian 1949, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Cuando Los Hijos Se Van 1941, 6 Stills (Box 5)
- Cuando Los Padres Se Quedan Solos 1948, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Cuando Quiero Llorar No Lloro 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Cuando Tejenlasaranas 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Cuando Tu Me Quieras 1950, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- 41 El Hombre Perfecto 1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Cuarto Chino, El 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Cuatro Noches Contigo 1951, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Cucurrucucu Paloma 1964, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Chanoc 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Chanoc En El Circo Union 1978, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Chanoc En El Foso De Las Serpientes 1974, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Chanoc En La Isla Delosmuertos 1975, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Charro Del Cristo, El 1949, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Charro Unmor Tal, El 1955, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Chico Ramos 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Chismoso De La Ventana, El 1955, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Choca, La 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Dama Del Alba, La 1965, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Depulqueroa Mill Onario 1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Debieronahorcarlos Antes 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Derecho A La Vida, El 1958, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Derecho De Na Cer, El 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Desarraigados, Los 1975, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Deseada 1950, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Despedida De Sol Tera 1965, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Despertar Del Lobo, El 1968, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 5)
- Dia De Las Madres, El 1968, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Dia De Los Asesinos, El 1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Diez Fusiles Esperi4n 1958, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Dile Que La Quiero 1963, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Dios, El Nino Yel Mar 1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Discotec Fin De Semana 1978, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Distrito Federal 1979, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Domingo Sal Vaje 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Dona Diabla 1949, 8 Stills (Box 6)
- Dos Caballeros De Espada 1963, 10 Stills (Box 6)
- Dos Carnales, Los 1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Dos Gallos De Pelea 1949, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Dos Maridos Bara Tos 1959, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Dos Mundos Y Unamor 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Dos Pintores Pintorescos 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Dos Ri Vales, Los 1965, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Dos Tontos 1 Un Loco 1960, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Doctor Satan Yla Magia Negra 1967, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Duda, La 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Duelo En El Desierto 1963, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Duelo En El Dorado 1968, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Duende y Yo, El 1960, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Duquesa Diabolica, La 1963, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- El Que No Corre Vuela 1980, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Emboscada Mortal 1960, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Emiliano Zapata 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- En Busca De Un Muro 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- En la Mitad Del Mundo 1963, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Enamorada 1946, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 6)
- Encuentro De Un Hombre Solo, El 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Ensa Y0 De Una Noche De Bodas 1967, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Espadachin, El 1963, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Esperame En Siberia, Vida Mia 1969, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Espiritismo 1961, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Esta Nocheno 1965, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Estatua De Carne, La 1951, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Estas Ruinas Que Ves 1978 (Box 7)
- Estrella Ydosestrellados, Una 1959, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Eugenia Grandet 1952, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- [?] 6 Dario 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- [? as] A La Moral 1969, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- [? Aste] Corazon 1969, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- [?] Ranchera 1943) A~,A~~Speranza Y Caridad, 1972 (Box 7)
- Felicidad 1956, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Fernandez De Feral Villo, Los 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Fiera, La 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Figuras de arena, Las 1969, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Fija Te Que Suave 1947, 8 Stills (Box 7)
- Flor De Durazno 1945, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Forajidos, Los 1962, 9 Stills (Box 7)
- Forastero Vengador, El 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Frenteal Pecado Deayer 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Fuerza Inutil, La 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Fuerzas Vivas, Las 1975, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Fuga De Carrasco, La 1983, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Fuga En la Noche 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Galleros De Jalisco, Los 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Gallo En Corral Ajeno, Un 1951, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 7)
- Garra Del Leopardo, La 1962, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Generaa, La 1970, 10 Stills (Box 8)
- Gran Casino 1946, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Granpillo, El 1958, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Grand Esaguas, Las 1978, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Guerra De Las Monjas, La 1968, 8 Stills (Box 8)
- Guerra Es Un B Uen Negocio, La 1982, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Guerrillera De Villa, La 1967, 9 Stills (Box 8)
- Guerrillero Del Norte, El 1982, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Guita Rras De Media Noche 1957, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Guitarras Lloren Guitarras 1964, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hacedor Del Miedo, El 1969, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hallazgo Sangriento 1984, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hasta El Viento Tiene Miedo 1967, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hembra Maldita, La 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hermanos Diablo, Los 1959, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hija De la Otra, La 1950, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hijos Del Condenado, Los 1964, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hijos Del Divorcio, Los 1957, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Historia De Un Gran amor 1942, 9 Stills (Box 8)
- Hombre De La Ametralladora, El 1960, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hombre Desnudo, El 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hombre Inquieto, El 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hombre Llamado El Diablo, Un 1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hombre Peligroso, Un 1964, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hombres De L Upe Al Virez, Los 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Hombres De Tierra Caliente 1983, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Huracanramirez Yla Monjita Negpla 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Idolo, El 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Imperio De La Fortuna, El 1985, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 8)
- Impostor, El 1956, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Increible Profesor Zovek, El 1971, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- India, La 1974, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Infierno Dealmas 1958, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Ingra Titud De Los Hijos, La 1962, 10 Stills (Box 9)
- Invasion De Los Muertos, La 1971, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Investigador Capulina, El 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Isla De Las Mujeres, La 1952, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Isla De Los Dinosa Urios, La 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Isla De Los Hombres Solos, La 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Isla Derarotonga, La 1980, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Islasmarias, Las 1950, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Jardin de Los Cerezos, El 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Jardin de Tia Isabel, El 1971, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Jesus El Nino Dios 1969, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Jovenjuarez, El 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Jovenmancornadora, La 1959, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Juez De La Soga, El 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Juicio De Los Hijos, El 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Juniors, Los 1969, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Justiciero Vengador, El 1960, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Juventud Desnuda 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Juventud Se Impone, La 1964, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Kaliman El Hombre Increible 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Karateca Azteca, El 1974, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Kid Tabaco 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Laberinto De Pasiones 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Ladron Fenomeno, El 1980, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- Ladrona, La 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- La Grimas De Mi Barrio 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 9)
- La Grimas Robadas 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Las del Talon 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Legitima Defensa 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Leones Del Ring, Los 1972, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Leyendas Ma Cabras De La Colonia 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Lina La Mujer De Fuego 1958, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Lio De Faldas 1969, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Lo Que le paso a Sanson 1955, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Locos Por La Musica 1958, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Locura Musical 1956, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Longitud De Guerra 1975, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Los Deabajo 1976, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Lucha Con La Pantera, La 1974, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Luna Desangre 1983, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Llamenme Mike 1979 (Box 10)
- Llanto De La Tor Tuga, El 1974), 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Llanto, Risas Yknock Out 1974, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Lluvia Roja 1949, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Macario 1959, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Madrina Del Diablo, La 1937) (Box 10)
- Maldita Ciudad 1954, Jj Stills (Box 10)
- Malditas Sean Las Mujeres 1936, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Mama, Soy Pa Quito 1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Manicomio 1957, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Manuel Saldivar El Texano 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Marca Desatanas, La 1956, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Marcel 0 Ymaria 1964, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Marchanta, La 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Marejada 1952, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Maria Pistolas 1962, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 10)
- Mariachi 1976, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Marido De Mi No Via, El 1950, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mariposas disecadas, Las 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Martir Del Cal Va Rio, El 1952, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Masalla De La Violencia 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mas Negro Que La Noche 1974, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mascara Dehierro, La 1959, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Matar Por Matar 1978, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Matenme Por Que Me Muero 1951, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Maternidad Imposible 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Me Cal De La Nube 1974, 11 Stills (Box 11)
- Me Gustan Todas 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Me Perdere Contigo 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Medico De Las Locas, El 1955, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mentira, La 1969, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mesera Del Café Del Puerto, La 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Meses Y Los Dm5, Los 1971, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Metiche, El 1970, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mexicano, El 1976, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mexicano, Tu Puedes 1983, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mexico De Noche 1974, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mexico Norte 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mi Aventura En Puerto Rico 1974, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mi Heroe 1964, 9 Stills (Box 11)
- Minino Tizoc 1971, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Miercoles De Ceniza 1958, Jj Stills (Box 11)
- Mil Y Una Noches, Las 1957, 11 Stills (Box 11)
- Minuto De Bondad, Un 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mis Abuelitas Nomas 1959, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mis Padres Se Di Vorcia N 1957, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mis Tres Viudasalegres 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Mision Cumplida 1968, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Momia Azteca, La 1957, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 11)
- Momias de Guanajuato, Las 1970, 9 Stills (Box 12)
- Momias De Sanangel, Las 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Monstruo De Los Volcanes, El 1962, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Montana Del Diablo, La 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Morena De Mi Copla, La 1945, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Morir Para Vivir 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Moro De Cumfas, El 1976, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Movida Chueca, Una 1955, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Mucha Chos De Barrio 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Muerte En Bikini, La 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Mujer Ajena, La 1954, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Mujer Cualquiera, Una 1949, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Mujer De Dos Caras, La 1955, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Mujer Mas, Una 1956, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Mujer Perfecta, La 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Mujer Que Yo Ferdi, La 1949, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Mujer Sin Lagrimas, La 1951, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Mujeres Del Faraiso 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Mujeres Enganadas 1960, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Mujeres Que Traba Jan 1952, 10 Stills (Box 12)
- Mundo Loco De Los Jo Venes, El 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Nacomasnaco, El 1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Napoleoncito 1963, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Naufragio 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Nazarin 1958, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Nimodo, Asisomos 1980, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Nino Del Tambor, El 1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 12)
- Nino Pobre, Nino Rico 1983, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Nino Y la Niebla, El 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- No Me Defiendas, Compadre 1949, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- No Oyes Ladrar Los Perros? 1974, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- No Tiene La Culpa El Indio 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Noche De Ferdicion 1951, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Noche Del Halcon, La 1967, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Noche Violenta, La 1969, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Noches De Pal Oma, Las 1977, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Noches Del Blanquita, Las 1981, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Norteno, El 1962, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Nos Dicen Las Intocables 1963, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Nosotras Las Sir Vientas 1951, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Novias Impacientes 1966, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Nuestro Juramento 1979, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Nuevo Mundo 1976, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Nunca Debieronamarse 1951, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Odalisca Numero 13, La 1957, 9 Stills (Box 13)
- Oficio Masantiguo Del Mundo, El 1968, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Ofrenda 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Organillero, El 1956, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Otra Virginidad, La 1974, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Pancho Lopez 1956, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Pandilla Enaccion, La 1959, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Pandillero, El 1959, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Para Todas hay1964, 10 Stills (Box 13)
- Fasajeros En Transito 1976, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Pasion Jarocha 1949, 7 Stills (Box 13)
- Pasionaria 1951, 7 Stills (Box 13)
- Paso A La Juventud 1957, 7 stills (Box 13)
- Pecado De Juventud 1961, 11 Stills (Box 13)
- Pegando Con Tubo 1960, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 13)
- Feligrosdejuventud 1959, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 14)
- Peluquero De Senoras 1971, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 14)
- Pena, Penita 1953, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 14)
- Peor Que Los Buitres 1973, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 14)
- Pepito Y Los Roba Chicos 1957, 12 Original b&w stills (Box 14)